Jasneet Kaur

HR Strategist | Talent Advisor | Change Leader



Contact

Phone: +91 9958089896 Email: Jasneet77@gmail.com Linkedin.com/in/jasneet-kaur

Critical experiences

- Functional Leadership
- Start-up Builder
- Culture Evangelism
- Change Management
- Transformation & Restructuring
- Mergers & Acquisition
- Resource & Process Optimization

Life & Style

- Walking is my Mantra
- Travel Enthusiast
- Drive for Delight
- Poetry for the Soul
- Tennis Student

Career Summary

Seasoned HR professional with 25 years of cross functional Human Resource experience across diverse industries with in-depth experience in Business Partnering, HR Consulting, Talent, Rewards, OD and HR Analytics; with geographic responsibilities spanning India, APAC, Europe, Middle East and North America.

Work Experience

SEPTEMBER 2021 TO PRESENT: PHILIP MORRIS INTERNATIONAL Head - People & Culture



Leading the People & Culture function for India affiliate, enabling and driving people strategy aligned to business Must Win Battles and outcomes.

AUGUST 2020 – SEPTEMBER 2021: BHARATPE Chief Human Resources Officer



Instrumental in building India's leading fintech start-up, a pioneer in UPI payments and digital money lending for merchants.

NOVEMBER 2017 - AUGUST 2020: SABBATICAL | ASSIGNMENTS







AUGUST 2017 - NOVEMBER 2018: PEPSICO Director - Human Resources & Workplace Experience



Led India Subcontinent Talent Management & OD; Learning; Total Rewards; Culture, Diversity & Inclusion; HR Operations; Employee Labor Relations; Facilities

MAERSK MAY 2012 - AUGUST 2017: MAERSK GLOBAL SERVICES India HR Head & Global Lead Org Restructuring, Integrated Resource Management, HR transformation (2014 – 2017) Global Lead for Performance, Rewards and HR Analytics (2012 – 14)

1999 - MAY 2012:

Industry Span: Life Sciences | IT-ITeS | FMCG | Logistics | Consulting | NGO









Accolades & Awards

- @Maersk: Titan of the Year for spearheading HR Transformation
- @Reliance: Employee of the year
- @Mercer: IPE specialist
- Part of winning teams across **DEI initiatives** across orgs.

References

Available on Request

Winning Projects

Incentive Plan Designs:

BYORC – Build Your Own Rewards & Controls @ PMI
BYOC – Build Your Own Compensation @ BharatPe
Global Incentive Plan @Maersk
Long Term Incentive Plan Design & Deployment @Jubilant Life Sciences

HR Transformation @Maersk

80:20 approach to global HR solutions RPO | Global Process Outsourcing | Resource Optimization

Project Trident @Maersk

Integrated Resources Management including Internal Talent Moves & External Hiring & Onboarding of 300+ resources within a span of 3 weeks towards resource fulfilment for a global tri-company merger.

EVP Playbook & Toolkit @PMI

Eye of PMI – A unique approach to solving business & culture imperatives eNPS growth by 40 basis points

Education

Human Resources Graduate Leadership Program - 2014

RBL Group, Utah, United States
Privileged personalized coaching with Dave Ulrich

Post Graduate Diploma in Business Management – HR & IT -1999 Institute of Management & Technology, Ghaziabad, India

Bachelors in Arts - Honors in Psychology - 1997

Punjab University, Chandigarh, India